### Yaron Pariente UX/UI Designer

Date of birth: 1976 • Address: Ramat Gan, Israel

Tel: (+972) 52-4503942 • Email: yaronsan2@gmail.com

\_\_\_\_

#### **About Me**

As a product designer with over than 15 years of experience in the digital field, I have a range of skills based on the knowledge I have acquired in my various roles. These skills give me the ability to better characterize the users and understand their changing needs, in order to design the product accordingly.

In the design process, I build the product after a thorough research that includes a full attention to the UX processes and a pixel perfect in UI, from the beginning till the final product.

My added value as a product designer lies in the ability to challenge the user's relationship with the product, with a genuine understanding of his or her sensibilities and desires.

- Experience with ownership of UX/UI design process.
- Ability to craft a prototypes and motion tools.
- Manage tasks according to set priorities.
- Specialty working directly with developers.

# **Professional Experience:**

see more details at my Linkedin page

**2018 - 2019** - UX/UI | Product Designer at:

Bitcard | Mobile/Desktop Wallet and Trade system design | (Crypto)

2017 - UX/UI Designer at:

<u>Playgorithm</u> | A social gaming experience

2014 - 2016 - UX/UI Designer at:

Grabbit | Second hand items app | Founder

2012 - 2015 - Art Director at:

Opticana | Design Studio Manager

2009 - 2011 - Establishing the company's Graphics Department at K. Amdor

2005 - 2009 - Owner of 'Digital Media Art' Studio.

### **Education:**

2016 - User Experience Course | Mentor Graphics Israel.

2014 - SolidWorks Course | Systematics Ltd.

2012 - Indesign Course | Mentor Graphics Israel.

2001 - 2005 - Design and Animation | Camera Obscura School of Arts.

## **Technical Skills:**

Sketch | Figma | Adobe Suite | Flinto | Among others

My Portfolio | http://yaronparienteportfolio.pp.ua LinkedIn | https://www.linkedin.com/in/pariente-yaron-1207a753/